ABHISHEK PATEL

Graphic & Web designer



Work Experience

People's University (2021-Present)

Graphic designer

Mesh Prints (2019-2021)

Graphic designer & Assistant manager

Preetam Enterprises (2018-2019)

Graphic designer & Assistant manager

Kailash printing press

Graphic designer & Computer Operator

Education

Sagar institute of research and technology (2017-21)

Bachelor of Technology (Information technology)

Govt. Boys higher secondary school

12th - Physics, Chemistry, Maths

Career Summary

Graphic Designer with over 5 years in Printing & Adv. Field. Highly skilled in Branding, Adv., Marketing, promotions. Have worked with highprofile clients.

Contact Person



7974518557



140, Semra, Bhopal - 462010



patelabhishek2212@gmail.com



patelabhishek2212.netlify.app

Personal information

Date of birth: 12 July 1999

Current Place: Bhopal

Father's Name: Mr. Shivraj Singh Patel

Nationality: Indian

Certification

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Basic Python
- Web design

Software Skills

- Coreldraw
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effect
- Canva

Coding Skills

- HTML & CSS
- Java Script
- Python

